School of Medicine Records UA010
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Office of the Dean, Subject files, 1882 -- 1989; UA010.002; 13.2 Linear Feet
  - Council of the dean, 1980 -- 1985; UA010.002.029.00025 (Box 29)
  - Council of the dean, 1986; UA010.002.029.00026 (Box 29)
  - Community affairs committee, 1971; UA010.002.029.00027 (Box 29)
  - Continuing education committee, 1977; UA010.002.029.00028 (Box 29)
  - Cosmetics, toiletry, and fragarency association, 1981; UA010.002.029.00029 (Box 29)
  - Counciling, policy and program committee, 1980; UA010.002.029.00030 (Box 29)
  - Clinical affairs committee, 1974; UA010.002.029.00031 (Box 29)
  - Clinical cancer education committee, 1975; UA010.002.029.00032 (Box 29)
  - Curriculum coordinators, 1982; UA010.002.029.00033 (Box 29)
  - Curriculum office, 1983; UA010.002.029.00034 (Box 29)
  - Curriculum update, 1980; UA010.002.029.00035 (Box 29)
  - Curriculum vitaes, 1982; UA010.002.029.00036 (Box 29)
  - Curriculum vitaes, 1982; UA010.002.029.00037 (Box 29)
  - Databook for overview of Tufts University school of medicine, 1981; UA010.002.030.00001 (Box 30)
  - Dean's advisory committee, 1980; UA010.002.030.00002 (Box 30)
  - Dean's advisory committee, 1975 -- 1982; UA010.002.030.00003 (Box 30)
  - Dean's advisory committee, 1975 -- 1982; UA010.002.030.00004 (Box 30)
  - Dean's advisory committee, 1983; UA010.002.030.00005 (Box 30)
  - Dean's advisory committee, 1983; UA010.002.030.00006 (Box 30)
  - Dean's advisory commitee, 1983; UA010.002.030.00007 (Box 30)
  - Dean's advisory council, 1983 -- 1984; UA010.002.030.00008 (Box 30)
  - Dean's weekly staff of managers, 1982 -- 1984; UA010.002.030.00009 (Box 30)
  - DeJong, Rudolph, 1980; UA010.002.030.00010 (Box 30)
  - Delmed inc, 1982; UA010.002.030.00011 (Box 30)
  - Deutsch, Carrol, 1983; UA010.002.030.00012 (Box 30)
  - Douglas, William, 1983; UA010.002.030.00013 (Box 30)
  - Douglas, William, 1983; UA010.002.030.00014 (Box 30)
  - Douglas, William, 1983; UA010.002.030.00015 (Box 30)
  - Durgin, William, 1983; UA010.002.030.00016 (Box 30)
  - Education affairs committee, UA010.002.030.00017 (Box 30)
  - Educational development, 1984 -- 1985; UA010.002.030.00018 (Box 30)
  - Educational development, 1979; UA010.002.030.00019 (Box 30)
  - Educational media, 1969 -- 1979; UA010.002.030.00020 (Box 30)
  - Educational media dept., 1980; UA010.002.030.00021 (Box 30)
  - Elliot, Clemence III, 1984; UA010.002.030.00022 (Box 30)
  - Elliot, Theodore L., 1985; UA010.002.030.00023 (Box 30)
  - Emergency medicine ad hoc committee, 1981; UA010.002.031.00001 (Box 31)
  - Emergency procedures, 1981; UA010.002.031.00002 (Box 31)
  - Environmental health committee, 1979; UA010.002.031.00003 (Box 31)
  - Environmental health program, UA010.002.031.00004 (Box 31)
  - Environmental protection agency, 1981; UA010.002.031.00005 (Box 31)
  - Enviromental policy roundtable, 1981; UA010.002.031.00006 (Box 31)
  - Epidemology biometry comm, 1980; UA010.002.031.00007 (Box 31)
  - Faculty promotions and appointments committee, 1983; UA010.002.031.00008 (Box 31)
  - Executive council, 1981 -- 1986; UA010.002.031.00009 (Box 31)
  - Executive council, 1981 -- 1986; UA010.002.031.00010 (Box 31)
  - Executive council, 1981 -- 1986; UA010.002.031.00011 (Box 31)
  - Faulkner hospital, 1973; UA010.002.031.00012 (Box 31)
  - Faculty roster, 1976 -- 1977; UA010.002.031.00013 (Box 31)
  - Faculty roster, 1976 -- 1977; UA010.002.031.00014 (Box 31)
  - Faculty roster, 1977 -- 1978; UA010.002.031.00015 (Box 31)
  - Faculty roster, 1977 -- 1978; UA010.002.031.00016 (Box 31)
  - Faculty roster, 1978 -- 1979; UA010.002.031.00017 (Box 31)
  - Faculty roster, 1978 -- 1979; UA010.002.031.00018 (Box 31)
  - Faculty roster, 1980 -- 1981; UA010.002.031.00019 (Box 31)
  - Faculty roster, 1980 -- 1981; UA010.002.031.00020 (Box 31)
  - Faculty (clinical) roster, 1978 -- 1980; UA010.002.031.00021 (Box 31)
  - Faculty (clinical) roster, 1979 -- 1980; UA010.002.031.00022 (Box 31)
  - Faculty roster, 1980; UA010.002.031.00023 (Box 31)
  - Fund raising study, 1977; UA010.002.031.00024 (Box 31)
  - Fund raising survey report, 1976; UA010.002.031.00025 (Box 31)
  - Foundation applications, UA010.002.031.00026 (Box 31)
  - Foster, Henry, 1983; UA010.002.031.00027 (Box 31)
  - Framingham union hospital, 1985; UA010.002.032.00001 (Box 32)
  - Frommer, Jack, 1985; UA010.002.032.00002 (Box 32)
  - Geriatrics, 1979; UA010.002.032.00003 (Box 32)
  - Glidden, H Spencer, 1982; UA010.002.032.00004 (Box 32)
  - Gowans, James DC, UA010.002.032.00005 (Box 32)
  - Handler, Eugene, 1983; UA010.002.032.00006 (Box 32)
  - Health manpower bill, 1974; UA010.002.032.00007 (Box 32)
  - Health policy committee, 1979; UA010.002.032.00008 (Box 32)
  - HSEB executive committee, 1983 -- 1985; UA010.002.032.00009 (Box 32)
  - HSEB executive committee, 1983 -- 1985; UA010.002.032.00010 (Box 32)
  - HSEB report, 1987 -- 1988; UA010.002.032.00011 (Box 32)
  - HSEB grant, 1981; UA010.002.032.00013 (Box 32)
  - HSEB grant, 1981; UA010.002.032.00014 (Box 32)
  - Health sciences library, flansburg report, 1971; UA010.002.032.00015 (Box 32)
  - Health sciences library, flansburg report, 1971; UA010.002.032.00016 (Box 32)
  - Health sciences library search commitee, 1982; UA010.002.032.00017 (Box 32)
  - Heymsfield, Steven B, UA010.002.032.00018 (Box 32)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, 1978 -- 1985; UA010.002.032.00019 (Box 32)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, 1978 -- 1985; UA010.002.032.00020 (Box 32)
  - HMO feasability study, 1977; UA010.002.032.00021 (Box 32)
  - Hughes, Walter L, 1982; UA010.002.032.00022 (Box 32)
  - Human investigations review committee, 1970 -- 1973; UA010.002.032.00023 (Box 32)
  - Human investigations review committee, 1974 -- 1976; UA010.002.032.00024 (Box 32)
  - Institutional self-study task force report, UA010.002.032.00025 (Box 32)
  - Johnson, Donald B, 1982; UA010.002.032.00026 (Box 32)
  - Kasden, S Charles, 1984; UA010.002.032.00027 (Box 32)
  - Kaven, John, 1982; UA010.002.032.00028 (Box 32)
  - Kennedy memorial, 1988; UA010.002.032.00029 (Box 32)
  - Kindzerske, John, 1982; UA010.002.032.00030 (Box 32)
  - Laboratory building committee, 1979; UA010.002.033.00001 (Box 33)
  - Lakeville hospital, 1989; UA010.002.033.00002 (Box 33)
  - Lanyon, Lance, 1983; UA010.002.033.00003 (Box 33)
  - Lawrence F quigley Memorial Hospital, 1982; UA010.002.033.00004 (Box 33)
  - Learning resource committee, 1975 -- 1983; UA010.002.033.00005 (Box 33)
  - Learning resource committee, 1975 -- 1983; UA010.002.033.00006 (Box 33)
  - Learning resource committee, 1975 -- 1983; UA010.002.033.00007 (Box 33)
  - Learning resource committee, 1975 -- 1983; UA010.002.033.00008 (Box 33)
  - Leavy, Robert I (MD, dean), 1982; UA010.002.033.00009 (Box 33)
  - Lefavor, John, 1984; UA010.002.033.00010 (Box 33)
  - Legal, 1989; UA010.002.033.00011 (Box 33)
  - Lemul Shattuck Hospital, 1970 -- 1980; UA010.002.033.00012 (Box 33)
  - Lemul Shattuck Hospital, 1970 -- 1980; UA010.002.033.00013 (Box 33)
  - Lever, Walter F, 1978; UA010.002.033.00014 (Box 33)
  - Lin, Chi Wei, 1976; UA010.002.033.00015 (Box 33)
  - Long, Leslie Sawin, 1987; UA010.002.033.00016 (Box 33)
  - Maine Medical Center, 1973 -- 1986; UA010.002.033.00017 (Box 33)
  - Maine Medical Center, 1973 -- 1986; UA010.002.033.00018 (Box 33)
  - Maine Medical Center, 1973 -- 1986; UA010.002.033.00019 (Box 33)
  - Martin, Elizabeth T, 1983; UA010.002.033.00020 (Box 33)
  - Martin, Williams, 1982; UA010.002.033.00021 (Box 33)
  - McCarthy, Kathryn A, 1979; UA010.002.033.00022 (Box 33)
  - Meade, Richard A, 1984; UA010.002.033.00023 (Box 33)
  - Medieros, Cardinal, 1983; UA010.002.033.00024 (Box 33)
  - Medical Dean's office, academic council, 1980; UA010.002.033.00025 (Box 33)
  - Medical Dean's office, 1980; UA010.002.033.00026 (Box 33)
  - Medical ed. datebase, sect. I-VI, 1977; UA010.002.033.00027 (Box 33)
  - Medical ed. datebase, sect. VIII-XIV, 1977; UA010.002.033.00028 (Box 33)
  - Medical ed. datebase, sect. XV, 1977; UA010.002.033.00029 (Box 33)
  - Medical ed. datebase, sect. XVI, 1977; UA010.002.033.00030 (Box 33)
  - Medical education database, UA010.002.034.00001 (Box 34)
  - Medical education database, UA010.002.034.00002 (Box 34)
  - Meinerth, Lawrence C, UA010.002.034.00003 (Box 34)
  - Middlesex county hospital, 1986; UA010.002.034.00004 (Box 34)
  - Milton Hospital, 1984; UA010.002.034.00005 (Box 34)
  - Mitchell, George W, 1974 -- 1979; UA010.002.034.00006 (Box 34)
  - Mitchell, George W, 1974 -- 1979; UA010.002.034.00007 (Box 34)
  - Mitus, Wladyslow, 1981; UA010.002.034.00008 (Box 34)
  - Moore, Francis, 1983; UA010.002.034.00009 (Box 34)
  - Moussa, Pierre MD, 1987; UA010.002.034.00010 (Box 34)
  - Mumford, George (dean), 1983; UA010.002.034.00011 (Box 34)
  - Myerson, Paul G, 1979 -- 1984; UA010.002.034.00012 (Box 34)
  - Nadeau, Daniel, 1984; UA010.002.034.00013 (Box 34)
  - Nashoba community hospital, 1987; UA010.002.034.00014 (Box 34)
  - Nasif, Ronald MD, 1985 -- 1986; UA010.002.034.00015 (Box 34)
  - NEMCH medical board, 1974 -- 1979; UA010.002.034.00016 (Box 34)
  - NEMCH medical board meeting, 1977; UA010.002.034.00017 (Box 34)
  - NEMCH medical board meeting, 1977; UA010.002.034.00018 (Box 34)
  - NEMCH medical board meeting, 1977; UA010.002.034.00019 (Box 34)
  - Nevada wiche, 1979; UA010.002.034.00020 (Box 34)
  - New England deans, 1980; UA010.002.034.00021 (Box 34)
  - New England memorial, 1987; UA010.002.034.00022 (Box 34)
  - Newton Wellesley Hospital, 1969 -- 1980; UA010.002.034.00023 (Box 34)
  - North Shore Children's Hospital, 1976 -- 1979; UA010.002.034.00025 (Box 34)
  - NWH, 1981; UA010.002.034.00026 (Box 34)
  - Occupational medicine committee, 1979; UA010.002.034.00027 (Box 34)
  - Office of planning and evaluation: curriculum, 1986; UA010.002.034.00028 (Box 34)
  - Office of planning and evaluation: curriculum, 1986; UA010.002.034.00029 (Box 34)
  - Orthopedics, 1986; UA010.002.034.00030 (Box 34)
  - Packwood, Bob, 1986; UA010.002.035.00001 (Box 35)
  - Page, lot B, Dr. symposium, UA010.002.035.00002 (Box 35)
  - Pai, Dr T U, 1976; UA010.002.035.00003 (Box 35)
  - Parents day, 1986; UA010.002.035.00004 (Box 35)
  - Parents day, 1988; UA010.002.035.00005 (Box 35)
  - Pattern B lecture hall, 1981; UA010.002.035.00006 (Box 35)
  - Patterson, James F, 1983; UA010.002.035.00007 (Box 35)
  - Paychecks, 1986; UA010.002.035.00008 (Box 35)
  - Pediatric clerkship review commitee, 1985; UA010.002.035.00009 (Box 35)
  - Pediatric clerkship review, 1982; UA010.002.035.00010 (Box 35)
  - Pediatric hospital database, 1982; UA010.002.035.00011 (Box 35)
  - Penobscot Bay Medical Center-Rockland, 1988; UA010.002.035.00012 (Box 35)
  - Personnel, 1974 -- 1979; UA010.002.035.00013 (Box 35)
  - Personnel committee reports, 1971 -- 1975; UA010.002.035.00014 (Box 35)
  - Physiology, annual reports, 1981 -- 1982; UA010.002.035.00015 (Box 35)
  - Physiology, annual reports, 1985 -- 1986; UA010.002.035.00016 (Box 35)
  - Physocal diagnosis, 1973 -- 1980; UA010.002.035.00017 (Box 35)
  - Polivy, Kenneth MD, UA010.002.035.00018 (Box 35)
  - Position emission tomography, 1982; UA010.002.035.00019 (Box 35)
  - Prematric summary, 1986; UA010.002.035.00020 (Box 35)
  - Prematric summary, 1986; UA010.002.035.00021 (Box 35)
  - Primary care committee, 1979; UA010.002.035.00022 (Box 35)
  - Pritchard, Craig, 1984; UA010.002.035.00023 (Box 35)
  - Proger, Samuel, 1985; UA010.002.035.00024 (Box 35)
  - Project hope, 1984; UA010.002.035.00025 (Box 35)
  - Prothrow stith, 1988; UA010.002.035.00026 (Box 35)
  - Property and equiptment, 1986; UA010.002.035.00027 (Box 35)
  - Publications committee, 1978; UA010.002.035.00028 (Box 35)
  - Quincy City Hospital, 1982; UA010.002.035.00029 (Box 35)
  - Radioisotope committee, UA010.002.035.00030 (Box 35)
  - Radiation hazards control group, UA010.002.035.00031 (Box 35)
  - Research, joint committee, UA010.002.035.00032 (Box 35)
  - Research management committee, 1984; UA010.002.035.00033 (Box 35)
  - Research protocol #98, UA010.002.035.00034 (Box 35)
  - Research symposium, 1989; UA010.002.036.00001 (Box 36)
  - Resources committee, 1981 -- 1982; UA010.002.036.00002 (Box 36)
  - Review: dept. of anatomy and cellular biology (dept data-base), UA010.002.036.00003 (Box 36)
  - Review: dept. of anatomy and cellular biology (Dept data-base), 1985; UA010.002.036.00004 (Box 36)
  - Review: dept. of anatomy and cellular biology (chairman's narrative), 1985; UA010.002.036.00005 (Box 36)
  - Rollika, Maria, 1984; UA010.002.036.00006 (Box 36)
  - Sackler, Arthur M., 1987; UA010.002.036.00007 (Box 36)
  - Sackler 3, 1986; UA010.002.036.00008 (Box 36)
  - Salem Hospital, UA010.002.036.00009 (Box 36)
  - Sandstead, Harold H, 1984; UA010.002.036.00010 (Box 36)
  - Schlossberg, Cassidy, 1981; UA010.002.036.00011 (Box 36)
  - Select scientific overview committee, 1982; UA010.002.036.00012 (Box 36)
  - Serrano, Nicholas O, 1987; UA010.002.036.00013 (Box 36)
  - Sharpe, Geoffrey W G, 1980; UA010.002.036.00014 (Box 36)
  - Space review committee, 1983; UA010.002.036.00015 (Box 36)
  - Special programs development committee, 1981; UA010.002.036.00016 (Box 36)
  - Standing committees, 1975 -- 1976; UA010.002.036.00017 (Box 36)
  - Steering committee minutes (HSEB), 1982; UA010.002.036.00018 (Box 36)
  - Steering committee minutes (HSEB), 1982; UA010.002.036.00019 (Box 36)
  - Steering committee minutes (HSEB), 1982; UA010.002.036.00020 (Box 36)
  - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1960 -- 1969; UA010.002.036.00021 (Box 36)
  - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1971 -- 1976; UA010.002.036.00022 (Box 36)
  - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1970 -- 1974; UA010.002.036.00023 (Box 36)
  - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1973 -- 1975; UA010.002.036.00024 (Box 36)
  - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1975 -- 1979; UA010.002.036.00025 (Box 36)
  - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1975 -- 1979; UA010.002.036.00026 (Box 36)
  - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1970 -- 1979; UA010.002.036.00027 (Box 36)
  - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1969; UA010.002.036.00028 (Box 36)
  - Student affairs committee, 1978; UA010.002.036.00029 (Box 36)
  - Student class officers, 1980; UA010.002.036.00030 (Box 36)
  - Student evaluations and promotions committee, 1985; UA010.002.036.00031 (Box 36)
  - Student health, 1969 -- 1978; UA010.002.036.00032 (Box 36)
  - Student promotions committee, 1974 -- 1984; UA010.002.036.00033 (Box 36)
  - Study of arbacet treatment, UA010.002.037.00001 (Box 37)
  - Study of diet, estrogen, and breast cancer, UA010.002.037.00002 (Box 37)
  - Study of the effects of interleukin 1, UA010.002.037.00003 (Box 37)
  - Study of the efficacy and safety of PY 108-068, UA010.002.037.00004 (Box 37)
  - Study of immunoglobulins in etiology of non-toxic multinodular goiter, UA010.002.037.00005 (Box 37)
  - Study of kidney transplant cytomegalovirus prevention, UA010.002.037.00006 (Box 37)
  - Study of lens hydration and tear osmolarity in humans during sleep, UA010.002.037.00007 (Box 37)
  - Study of medullary thyroid carcinoma, UA010.002.037.00008 (Box 37)
  - Study of motor deficit in neuromuscular disease, UA010.002.037.00009 (Box 37)
  - Study of plasmapheresis in lupus nephritis, UA010.002.037.00010 (Box 37)
  - St. Vincent's Hospital, 1986; UA010.002.037.00011 (Box 37)
  - Sullivan, John F, 1969 -- 1978; UA010.002.037.00012 (Box 37)
  - Talamo, Richard C, 1979 -- 1980; UA010.002.037.00013 (Box 37)
  - Task force on curriculum planning, 1984; UA010.002.037.00014 (Box 37)
  - Task force on primary care and family, 1975; UA010.002.037.00015 (Box 37)
  - TUSM adhoc affiliation committee, 1972; UA010.002.037.00016 (Box 37)
  - TUSM affiliation agreements, 1975; UA010.002.037.00017 (Box 37)
  - TUSM affiliation agreements, 1975; UA010.002.037.00018 (Box 37)
  - TUSM affiliation data, 1975; UA010.002.037.00019 (Box 37)
  - TUSM affiliation data, 1975; UA010.002.037.00020 (Box 37)
  - TUSM affiliated hospitals, 1972 -- 1973; UA010.002.037.00021 (Box 37)
  - TUSM affiliated hospitals, 1972 -- 1973; UA010.002.037.00022 (Box 37)
  - TUSM affiliated hospitals nos. of house staff, UA010.002.037.00023 (Box 37)
  - TUSM clinical affairs committee, UA010.002.037.00024 (Box 37)
  - TNEMC information, 1968; UA010.002.037.00025 (Box 37)
  - TNEMC information, 1968; UA010.002.037.00026 (Box 37)
  - University computer committee, 1981 -- 1982; UA010.002.037.00027 (Box 37)
  - University council meetings, 1981 -- 1986; UA010.002.037.00028 (Box 37)
  - University faculty committee advisory board, 1982; UA010.002.037.00029 (Box 37)
  - Veteran's administration hospital, 1967; UA010.002.037.00030 (Box 37)
  - Walker bailus public health, 1986; UA010.002.037.00031 (Box 37)
  - Ward, Graham W, 1982 -- 1983; UA010.002.037.00032 (Box 37)
  - Whitaker funds papers, 1985; UA010.002.037.00033 (Box 37)
  - Whitaker funds papers, 1985; UA010.002.037.00034 (Box 37)
  - Williams, Alice C, 1979 -- 1982; UA010.002.037.00035 (Box 37)
  - Wolfson, Louis E, 1958 -- 1964; UA010.002.037.00036 (Box 37)
  - Wolfson, Louis E, 1958 -- 1964; UA010.002.037.00037 (Box 37)
  - Women's and Children's Hospital, 1964 -- 1982; UA010.002.037.00038 (Box 37)
  - Zimniak, Piotr, 1985; UA010.002.037.00039 (Box 37)
- Faculty meeting and committee minutes, 1893 -- 1976; UA010.003; 1.7 Linear Feet
  This series consists of nine volumes of minutes of the meetings of the faculty and several different committees in the Medical School: the Executive Committee, Administrative Committee, the Committee on Instruction, and the Admissions Committee.
  Faculty meeting minutes run from 1893-1914; Executive Committee minutes run from 1897-1902; Administrative Committee minutes run from 1902-70; Committee on Instruction minutes run from 1905-13; and Admission Committee minutes from 1921-25.
  This series is arranged chronologically and by size when applicable.
  - Faculty meeting and Executive Committee minutes, 1893 -- 1899; UA010.003.043.00001 (Box 43)
  - Faculty meeting, Executive Committee, and Administration Committee minutes, 1899 -- 1905; UA010.003.043.00002 (Box 43)
  - Administrative Committee and Committee on Instruction minutes, 1905 -- 1910; UA010.003.043.00003 (Box 43)
  - Faculty meeting minutes, 1905 -- 1914; UA010.003.043.00004 (Box 43)
  - Administrative Committee minutes, 1910 -- 1914; UA010.003.043.00005 (Box 43)
  - Committee on Instruction minutes, 1910 -- 1913; UA010.003.043.00006 (Box 43)
  - Administrative Committee minutes, 1914 -- 1953; UA010.003.043.00007 (Box 43)
  - Faculty meeting minutes and Hospital Committee minutes, 1914 -- 1953; UA010.003.043.00008 (Box 43)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1953 -- 1963; UA010.003.043.00009 (Box 43)
  - Admissions Committee minutes, 1921 -- 1925; UA010.003.044.00001 (Box 44)
  - Reel No. 63-29: School of Medicine Faculty Minutes, 1934 -- 1963; UA010.003.044.00002 (Box 44)
  - Administrative Committee minutes and Executive Faculty minutes, 1964 -- 1976; UA010.003.044.00003 (Box 44)
  - Faculty meeting minutes, 1965 -- 1969; UA010.003.044.00004 (Box 44)
- Photographs, teaching materials, and programs, 1893 -- 2019; 1897 -- 1937; UA010.004; 6.2 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s); 2 Digital Object(s)
  Custodial History
  This series was created for one medical school photograph, on the assumption that more medical school photographs would eventually be forthcoming. Medical school materials were also added to the collection after the discovery of several items.
  This series is not arranged.
  This series contains photographs, lectures, and examination materials related to the Tufts University School of Medicine.
  - Tufts College Medical School campaign dinner, 1937-10-27; UA010.004.042.00001; Fay Foto (Box Shared 35)
    The campaign dinner was held at the University Club, Boston, Mass., October 27, 1937.
    People; Dinners and Dining; Men; photographic print; Tufts College; School of Medicine
  - Alpha Kappa Kappa (Gamma Chapter), 1898; UA010.004.042.00002 (Box Shared 35)
    This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2007. Note on ALPHA KAPPA KAPPA AND THE GAMMA CHAPTER: MEDICAL SCHOOL: The Alpha Kappa Kappa Society was organized by several students of the Dartmouth Medical School in 1888. It is strictly a medical society, its aims being the advancement of Medical Science and the promotion of good fellowship. The Beta Chapter of Alpha Kappa Kappa is located at the University of Vermont. The Gamma Chapter was instituted at the Tufts Medical School during the Spring term of 1894, Professor Charles P. Thayer standing as its godfather. It has grown steadily, and fully realized the expectations of its founders. It at present occupies rooms on Boylston Place, but is soon to move into more commodious quarters. The meetings of the Chapter are held bi-monthly. Source: "History of Tufts College," Alaric Bertrand Start, 1896 (Tufts Digital Library)
    photographic print
  - Medical School, 1912; UA010.004.042.00003 (Box Shared 4)
    This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2007. Note its different location; it is housed in a separate box with other oversize materials.
  - Class Photo, 1912; UA010.004.042.00004 (Box Shared 4)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine, 1966; UA010.004.042.00005 (Box Shared 35)
    This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. Tear along left side of photograph. Information on back concerning painter of work.
  - Tufts University School of Medicine, 1966; UA010.004.042.00006 (Box Shared 35)
    This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008.
  - Twentieth Anniversary Reunion, Tufts Medical College, Class of 1919, 1939; UA010.004.042.00007 (Box Shared 35)
  - Tufts College Medical School, 1911; UA010.004.042.00008 (Box Shared 36)
    This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in the summer of 2008. Note its different location; it is housed in a box with other oversize materials.
  - Medical School examination book, 1893 -- 1903; UA010.004.042.00009 (Box Shared 36)
    These dates are approximate. Note its different location; it is housed in a box with other oversize materials.
  - Book of lectures on histology, 1920 -- 1921; UA010.004.042.00010 (Box Shared 36)
    This item was found uncataloged in the stacks in the winter of 2009. Note its different location; it is housed in a box with other oversize materials.
  - The Alpha Omega Alpha honor medical society, 1940; UA010.004.042.00011 (Box Shared 36)
    This item was found uncataloged in the stacks in Winter 2009. Note the location. This item is housed with other oversized materials.
  - Professor Cadis Phipps, 1946; UA010.004.042.00012.000001 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    This image was found uncatalogued in the stacks in January 2009. Note its different location; it is housed in a separate box with other oversize materials.
  - Framed portrait of Professor Cadis Phipps (with inscription), 1932; UA010.004.042.00013 (Box Shared 8)
    Inscribed "To my dear friend Robert Phillips, Cadis Phipps, February 26, 1932". This image was found uncatalogued in the stacks in January 2009.
    paintings (visual works)
  - Diploma for Helen Semenenko, 1928; UA010.004.042.00014 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    Received from the Health Sciences Library on 2009-02-10. HSL Librarian Fran Foret indicated that it was donated by Semenenko's grandson. Records Archivist removed diploma from frame at time of accession. The following was written on the edge of the frame: June 18, 28 Date of Graduation 12915-8.
    poster
  - Officials of North Bolivar County Health Council meeting at Tufts to discuss Mound Bayou, 1909 -- 1970; UA010.004.DO.04624; Jet Commercial Photographers (Box Shared 37)
    Identified on back: "Man away from camera on far left, Jack Geiger, TUSM."
    People; Meetings; photographic print; School of Medicine
  - School of Medicine graduating class photograph, 1940; UA010.004.042.00012.000002; .2 Linear Feet (Box Shared 36)